http://www.skyauction.com/privacy.do

Skip to page contentOver 1,199,069 auction winners since 1999Best Prices Guaranteed!HomeLog inRegisterSearchCustomer CareDestinationsUSA & CanadaEuropeMexicoCaribbean & BahamasCentral AmericaSouth AmericaAsiaAustralia & South PacificAfrica & Middle EastHotelsCruisesAirSpecialty AuctionsDining & EntertainmentJewelryWatchesFashion AccessoriesSunglassesComputers & ElectronicsCollectablesSports MemorabiliaDiscount CertificatesHome & HealthMiscellaneousVacation RentalsHot OffersHot OffersDeals of the DayWhat's NewClosing SoonPrivacy PolicySkyAuction.com has created this privacy policy statement in order to
demonstrate our commitment to privacy. The following discloses the
information gathering and dissemination practice for the SkyAuction.com
web site. Using the Internet should be a fun experience and we want
to help you make it so.
When you reserve or purchase travel services or other products
through SkyAuction.com, we will ask you to provide us with personal
information, such as your name, mailing address, e-mail address,
credit card information and other personal identifying information.
We need this information in order to process your order or travel
arrangements and need to share this personal information with the
relevant airline, car rental agency, hotel, travel agency and/or
other involved third party.
As a user of SkyAuction.com, you have the option to engage in
certain additional activities on the site, such as entering
contests or sweepstakes, and receiving our e-mail alerts. It is
completely optional for you to engage in these activities. If you
elect to engage in these activities, however, SkyAuction.com may
require you to provide us with personal information, such as your
name, mailing address, e-mail address, and other personal
identifying information. SkyAuction.com needs to
collect this personal information for various reasons, which
may include: (i) notifying sweepstakes or contest winners,
(ii) fulfilling prizes; (ii) disseminating our e-mail;
(iii) aggregating statistical information; and (iv) tracking
and verifying compliance with SkyAuction.com policies and international,
federal, state and local laws.
SkyAuction.com recognizes and respects the importance of
responsible use of your personal information. If you do not
want the information you provide to SkyAuction.com to be used to
inform you of other products and special offers from SkyAuction.com,
and you indicate this preference when you provide the information,
SkyAuction.com will honor your preference. In case you change your
mind or some personal information may change (such as your zip code),
we provide a way to correct, update or remove the personal data you
give us. You can do this at the member information page or by
contacting our Customer Support organization.
OPTING-OUTTo keep you in control of your personal information and the
or by modifying your member information online.
Information provided when reserving or purchasing travel
services through SkyAuction.com, may be used for marketing and
promotional purposes and is subject to the opt-out processes
described on, or linked to, each order form.
THIRD PARTY ADVERTISINGWe use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when
you visit our Web site. These companies may use information
(not including your name, address, email address or telephone number)
about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide
advertisements on this site and other sites about goods
and services that may be of interest to you.
THIRD PARTY COOKIESIn the course of serving advertisements to this site, our
third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie"
on your browser.
We, or a data provider we have engaged, may place or recognize
a unique cookie on your browser to enable you to receive customized
ads, content or services. No personally identifiable information is
placed into these cookies.
The cookies may reflect de-identified
demographic or other data linked to data you voluntarily have
submitted to us, e.g., your email address, in hashed, non-human
readable form. To opt-out of these cookies or learn more please
go to http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.Additionally, emails we send may contain a bit of code known
as a "web beacon." This code allows us to understand the
time and date of when a user has opened an email and when he/she
has utilized a link within the email to visit a website. Our web
beacons do not collect personally identifiable information. Users
wishing to disable our web beacons should do so by turning images
"off" in their email client (e.g., Outlook, Outlook Express).
Please see your email client for more information."USE OF TRAFFIC DATAEach time a visitor comes to our Web site, we collect some
information to improve the overall quality of the online experience.
This includes the visitor's IP address, referral data (e.g., the
the address of the last URL a user visited prior to clicking
through to the SkyAuction.com Web site), and browser information.
We collect visitor information for purposes of product monitoring,
product improvement, and targeted advertising. We also count,
track, and aggregate all visitors' activity into our analysis
of general traffic flows at our sites (e.g., tracking where
traffic comes from, how traffic flows within the SkyAuction.com
properties, etc.). To these ends, we may merge information
about you into group data, which may then be shared on an
aggregated basis with our advertisers; but SkyAuction.com will not
disclose your individual identity or personal data without your
permission. When SkyAuction.com does present aggregated information
to outside companies, no one is able to identify you or contact you.
USE OF IP ADDRESSESAn IP address is a number that's associated with your computer
whenever you're surfing the Web. Web servers use your IP address to
communicate with your computer.
SkyAuction.com collects IP addresses for the purposes of system
administration, to report aggregate, or combined, information to
our advertisers, and to audit the use of our site. When users
request pages from the SkyAuction.com Web site, our servers log
the user's IP addresses. We do not normally link IP addresses
to anything personally identifiable, which means that your session
will be logged, but you remain anonymous to us. We can and will use
IP addresses to identify a user when we feel it is necessary to
enforce compliance with our rules or terms of service or to protect
our service, site, customers or others.
USE OF e-mail DATASkyAuction.com will use your e-mail address to send correspondence
about reservation confirmations, purchases, important updates about
your travel	plans, and newsletters. Members who sign up to receive
newsletters and notifications of deals and travel specials, will
receive a reguarly scheduled newsletter, as well as occasional
product-related announcements.Users can choose to unsubscribe from SkyAuction.com newsletters or
product-related announcements at any time by following the unsubscribe
instructions found in each e-mail or by
contacting our Customer Support organization.
CONTESTS AND SWEEPSTAKESSkyAuction.com offers contests and sweepstakes in which we request
certain personal information. At a minimum, the required information
includes name and e-mail address; in some cases, the user must
answer survey questions about a range of other personal data. The
information gathered in the entry form is used to verify the entrant's
identity and to contact winners and/or prize recipients. Participation
in these contests and sweepstakes is completely voluntary and the
user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this
information. There are two situations in which SkyAuction.com will
divulge this information to a third party provided the user gives
express consent: (1) A user may expressly choose to receive
additional information from the contest sponsor, in which case
the user's personally identifiable information is divulged to
the advertiser; (2) Some of the contests may be hosted on the
SkyAuction.com site but administered by the sponsor; in such
cases, the information a user provides is passed on to the third
party as long as that user gives express consent. Because the rules
and terms of each contest and sweepstakes can vary, all information
about each contest and sweepstakes is clearly posted during the event.
SURVEYSOccasionally SkyAuction.com conducts user surveys to better
target our content to our audience. Participation in these surveys
is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice
whether or not to disclose this information. We sometimes share
the aggregated demographic information in these surveys with our
advertisers and partners. We never share any personally
identifiable information with such third parties.
LINKS TO OTHER SITESUsers should be aware that when you are on the SkyAuction.com website,
could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. There are
links to other sites from SkyAuction.com pages that take you outside
our service. For example, if you click on a banner advertisement or
a SkyAuction.com more information link, the click takes you off
the SkyAuction.com site. This includes, but is not limited to,
links from advertisers, sponsors and partners that may use
SkyAuction.com logo as part of a co-branding agreement. These other
sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data or solicit
personal information.
This privacy policy does not extend to such third parties' use of such
information, anything that is inherent in the operation of the Internet,
and therefore beyond the control of SkyAuction.com, and is not to be
applied in any manner contrary to applicable law or governmental
regulation. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our
site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site
that collects personally identifiable information.
SECURITYSkyAuction.com has taken strong measures to protect the
security of your personal information and to ensure that your
choices for its intended use are honored. We take strong precautions
to protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or
disclosure, alteration, or destruction.
The importance of security for all personally identifiable
information associated with our guests is of utmost concern to us.
We exercise great care in providing secure transmission of your
information from your PC to our servers. Unfortunately, no data
transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.
As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information,
SkyAuction.com can not ensure or warrant the security of any information
you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do
so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our
best effort to ensure its security on our systems. When credit
card information is transmitted we use industry standard,
SSL (secure socket layer) encryption. SSL is a coding system that
lets your browser automatically encrypt, or scramble data before
you send it to us.Unfortunately, we cannot ensure that all of your private
communications and other personally identifiable information
will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in
this Privacy Policy.
By way of example (without limiting the
foregoing), we may be forced to disclose information to the
government or third parties under certain circumstances, or
third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions
or private communications.
We can (and you authorize us to)
disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other
government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe
necessary or appropriate, in connection with an investigation
of fraud, intellectual property infringement or other activity
that is illegal or may expose us to legal liability.
Therefore,
although we will endeavor to protect your privacy as described
in this Privacy Policy, we do not promise, and you should not
expect, that your personally identifiable information or
private communications will remain private.
Your SkyAuction.com account is password protected so that only
you can access it and view the member information relevant to the
account. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to
anyone. SkyAuction.com will never ask you for your password in
an unsolicited phone call or e-mail. Ultimately, you are
responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords
and any account information.YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMSBy using this site, you signify your assent to the
SkyAuction.com Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy,
please do not use our sites. Your continued use of the SkyAuction.com
Web site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean
you accept those changes. Any such change, update or modification
will be effective immediately upon posting to the SkyAuction.com
Web site.CONTACTING THE WEB SITEIf you have any questions about this privacy statement,
the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site,
Westfield, NJ 07090Last Updated June 23, 2017WelcomeAbout UsResourcesAdvertisingSite MapPlaces
Join us on:Privacy PolicyTerms of UseCopyright © 1999-2020 SkyAuction.com, Inc.
